Mm I think you need a dose of Vitamin Me
うだるような暑さ
垂れ下がった目尻
眠ってしまいそうな君
You need some of my citrus
弾けた一滴
想いを込めたsqueeze
壊れた君の心にtouch
You'll be like oh
いち に さん
心をrefresh
爽やかなLime juice
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
好きな色を 自由に混ぜて
一気に飲み干して
I'll mix it up On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
甘いLemon fizz
love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
高鳴るheartbeat
夜のない陽射し Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
君の一日を照らすには
ぬるい風は足りない
Cause I'm
Feeling you just come alive
I'm the best pick me up that you ever had
怠けた君の心臓を高鳴らせる
君が望んでた歌をsing along
Like oh
いち に さん 心をrefresh
真っ赤なgrapefruit
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
好きな色を 自由に混ぜて
一気に飲み干して
I'll mix it up
On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
甘いLemon fizz
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
高鳴るheartbeat
夜のない陽射し Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
君だけを照らすspotlight
誰にも内緒で
Maybe Maybe you've
Changed Changed me now
君となら何でもいい
真夏のdreamy
満ちていくsparkling
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
爽やかでwavy
高鳴るheartbeat
夜のない陽射し Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME